(Past Sheldon:)Come, I'll show you
the rest of the apartment.
(Past Leonard:)Good. I passed the barriers.
(Past Sheldon:)The second barrier. Don't get cocky.
(Past Sheldon:)This is the bathroom.
(Past Sheldon:)Are you fairly regular?
(Past Leonard:)-Uh-- I guess.
-This isn't going to work if you're guessing.
(Past Sheldon:)When do you evacuate your bowels?
(Past Leonard:)When I have to.
(Past Sheldon:)When you have to?
I'm sorry, I don't rent to hippies.
I'm sorry, in the morning. Around 8.
I can't give you 8. I can give you 7:30.
(Past Leonard:)Fine, I'll take it.
(Past Sheldon:)Third barrier passed.
(Past Sheldon:)You have won the right to see your room.
Pizah.
(Past Leonard:)-Is this it?
-No, this is my room.
(Past Sheldon:)People don't go in my room.
So where do you sleep? Heh.